[music]
>> My 15-minute makeup routine.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Good morning everyone. It is around 6:15
in the morning and I have to catch the
train to go into the office today for
work. I'm going to pack my work bag and
then see if I can do a little bit of my
makeup before I leave, but I'm not sure
I'm going to have enough time, so I
might do it on the train. I'm definitely
not a morning person, so waking up at
6:00 a.m. [music] is definitely hard for
me still, but I will say having some
morning sun definitely helps. [music]
Feel like it's literally just so pretty.
I got this new top in and I feel like
it's perfect for work, especially in the
summer because it's like nice and light.
But normally I would wear it without the
top on the inside, but I'm wearing work,
so
that's why I have it on the inside. Kind
of reminds me of that blue peplum top
that I got from Copenhagen.
Oh my god, I swear to god if I hear that
alarm one more time, bruh.
>> [music]
>> Think I have just enough time to do a
10-minute glam, so then don't have to
bring my entire makeup bag. I'm not
staying overnight in Toronto, so the
bag's not going to be like too too
heavy, but ideally my work bag is as
light as possible. So, maybe I won't.
I'm going to try to get it done. If you
guys are in person or internships or any
of your jobs, I'm curious to know if you
do your makeup or not because
>> [sighs]
>> I'm kind of like so I know that there is
like a societal standard [music]
for like women to be like put together
and you know, women are policed in a lot
of ways, especially in like appearance
in general. This has nothing to do with
my current workplace. They could not
care less about like how you dress. I
don't really know. I don't really know.
Kind of too early for me to be super
coherent, but essentially I wish we
lived in a world where it didn't matter
what you looked like at the workplace
and women were treated the same whether
they wore makeup or not. I did not wear
makeup whenever I worked at the pharmacy
either. Only on
I know on my first day.
>> Been a beauty blender girl my entire
life, but once I started using this
foundation stick, I switched over to a
like a kabuki brush and it's actually
really good. Like I'm so surprised
because I feel like I was always told
that makeup brushes will make your face
like look like streaky, but I think it
honestly looks fine. And it's low-key
way faster. I've also [snorts]
been seriously missing wearing over-ear
headphones because
Oh
my
>> [groaning]
[sighs and gasps]
>> I do this to myself because I always hit
snooze, but oh my god, that actually
grinds my gears.
Oh my god.
Sorry. Need to like not crash out, but
bro. As I was saying, I haven't been
able to wear the over-ear headphones
since I got my helix done and I think
it's been like 3 [music] weeks now, but
it's too long. I don't want to like
irritate it or anything because I know
that Asians are actually more prone to
getting keloids or like I don't know if
irritation bumps, but keloids for sure.
I'm just worried about that, [music] so
>> [music]
>> Don't get me wrong. I freaking love
doing makeup, but I feel like I still
need a little bit of setting powder just
to make sure that the makeup stays on.
>> [music]
>> Bro. Okay, I do have to leave soon, so
it's fine.
Okay, I think this is the final look. I
have to do my lips for sure.
Okay, guys. This is the final look of my
15-minute makeup routine. And now, let's
head into work.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I am finally done the work day. It is
5:46.
>> [music]
>> Thank you, Amanda. It looks so good.
[music]
>> Hi, guys. It is basically the middle of
the work day. I just got home so late
last night that I took the morning at
really slow, but there's still a couple
tasks I need to do for work. And I also
want to show you my nails. I don't know
if I really got a good shot. I think the
oral nail really came out perfectly. And
then actually going to have a really
crafty evening. So, let's finish off
this work day.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Guys, I'm getting such a blast from the
past right now because there was a point
in time where I was really interested in
like UX and I was trying to learn
[music] Figma. And I was just working
like FigJam the other day and now
[music] I'm in like Lucid AI or
Lucidchart, I think is the name. So, I
was using FigJam when I was making a
clinical workflow, but then I was using
Lucidchart and Lucid AI to make a
different workflow because Lucid AI
really made it easy to do. Anyways, I
just feel like it's a full circle moment
that 2 years ago I was trying to learn
Figma as like a hobby and then now I get
to use it in my internship.
>> [music]
>> Guys, I just got the most exciting thing
in the mail. I have to unbox this right
now.
Okay, I put the sticker paper in.
Looking perfect. [music]
I'm using the 4x7 sticker paper. I'm
going to just click print. Oh my god!
So, it's printing in yellow first.
Oh my god, this is so cool! Oh my gosh,
you guys! What? Look at the sticker
sheet. Okay, now the sheet is [music]
being laminated and then the stickers
are waterproof.
Okay, you guys. I was way too excited
earlier, so spoiler, I already printed
and cut out a sticker sheet. But, this
is the Liyana Phomemo S1. And this is
the world's first smart printing [music]
and cutting all-in-one machine. So, this
is the printing end and then this is the
cutting end. And actually the entire
print, laminate, and cut process is all
[music] automatic. Like, if you guys
just look at my phone, you know how much
I love stickers. And I just printed
these ones. And Liyana actually has a
really extensive template gallery.
There's literally like thousands of
designs that you could print. And all
the designs are free. [music] Look at
this one. gosh. And the app actually has
AI auto cutting. So, it can
automatically recognize and extract
[music] images, and you don't have to
manually adjust the borders or anything.
And the cutting technology of this
machine is actually so precise. And you
can also set a zero margin crop in the
app if you want to maximize your sticker
sheet. And these stickers are also super
high quality [music] and durable.
They're waterproof, UV resistant,
scratch resistant. So, they're perfect
if you want to put them in any
high-touch areas, whether it's your
laptop, water bottle, or [music]
notebook. Also, this entire process is
wireless. I just downloaded the app and
connected the printer to my phone via
Bluetooth. There's also a brand new AI
lab [music] that supports face swapping
and the generation of cartoon patterns
or like characters. There's also the
option to photo print. So, you can take
a photo of whatever you want and turn it
into a sticker.
So, if you guys have been wanting to get
crafty and make your own stickers, then
this is the perfect time to check out
Liyana because they are running a huge
[music] Amazon Prime Day sale. So, if
you want a promo code to save or link to
shop, make sure to check out the
description box below. I got too
excited, so I already started sticking
them onto my journal, but I just printed
this other sheet, and it looks so good.
You guys know I [music] love seafood, so
I had to print this one. I'm thinking
about what to put
I have to do
the tin fish cuz you guys know how much
I love tin fish.
Oh, that's so cute. I love it so much.
My journal's getting full.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Wait, where's the junk food one? Oh my
gosh.
>> Stunning.
>> I know I printed that one for the cast.
>> Beautiful. Why is his head
gigantic?
>> of the boy.
>> Oh, buddy, we got to get the big one.
>> of the boy. You're thinking of the boy.
You're thinking of the boy. You're
thinking of the boy.
>> Oh, that's going to be like so cute.
>> I know.
>> Hey guys, we're having a sister hangout
at Amanda's. We're having a co-working
day, and I also brought the stickers
that I printed from the Leanne Picks
Cut, so we can decorate our journals.
>> This is my journal right now. Cass is
decorating her laptop.
>> so cute.
>> She also designed some stickers for her
like wedding, and so I printed a bunch
of them for like wedding stationary.
>> My journal progress. I have a little
quote from Taylor Swift.
>> that goose one. Wait, certified silly
goose?
>> I have silly goose juice.
>> Oh my gosh. Oh my god, wait. This is so
funny.
>> I know. I was just trying to represent
us.
>> Look at Luna. [music]
>> Luna.
>> How many girls does it How many Quans
does it take to put on a screen door?
There's two out of three right now.
>> Oh, they're right there.
>> It's crooked.
>> No, it's not.
Tell me this is not.
>> It is crooked.
>> not.
It's mine. Here, it's mine.
>> Leave it.
>> Okay, I need help finding my audio.
Oh, I TOOK IT OUT.
>> NO!
IT WAS LIKE THREE PEOPLE.
>> OH, actually it's done now.
>> Oh, you found a piece. Amanda's getting
married.
>> Oh, it's like a nice mosquito net.
>> Oh.
Look at it. How much you pay for that?
$500?
>> It works.
>> Oh, that's so pretty.
>> Oh my god.
>> I I love that it's not like such a
bright white. It's like a
>> it.
>> Or like a cream.
>> [music]
>> I don't know.
>> Here you go.
>> [music]
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you so much.
Ice cream.
It's a work break.
>> [music]
>> Oh.
Oh. Oh my god, this is going to be so
good. This does not look appetizing
whatsoever, but it's going to be so
good.
>> Mhm. It kind of looks a little bit
scary. Oh.
Scary. That's It looks like a
questionable liquid.
>> I know. It looks like mystery soup.
Oh my god,
>> [music]
>> wait.
We're probably going to
>> [music]
[music]